Paulo Junior

Unity Developer Braga / Portugal

Master's degree student in Game Design and Development, with over 6 years of experience in software development. Passionate about games and development, study and develop projects in Unity for 4 years, always looking to learn and improve my development skills in C#. With the goal and dream of working in the gaming industry.

Education

Master's degree, Game Design and Development University Beira do Interior - Portugal

and a meeting

2019- Present

Currently studying, where I had the opportunity to learn about different areas of game development and design with projects and studies.

Now I am in the process of developing my thesis for the master's degree, which has as its theme, "The influence of electronic sports on the balance of games: The Dota 2 case"

Bachelor of Computer Information Systems

University Estácio de Sá - Brazil 2009- 2015

Work Experience

Software Engineer

Novovale Administração E Tecnologia **2014 - 2020**

- Development PHP system, Front-end and Back-end.
- Developer in a project developed in Arduino/ NodeMcu, C/C++.
- Development of all websites and web systems used by the company.

Information Technology Intern

Tribunal de Justiça do Estado do Rio de Janeiro **2013-2014**

Development PHP system, Front-end and Back-end, CMS.

E-mail:

paulojorgejunior@gmail.com

Games Projects:

In the link below you can see some game projects that I developed.

paulojjunior.github.io/portfolio

Skills

Unity
C#
PHP
HTML/CSS
C/C++
Photoshop
GIT

Personal Skills

I am a focused, participative person, I enjoy working in a team, and yet I am independent to work alone, I have no problems with criticism, and I am always open to a new challenge.

Languages

English: B1

Portuguese: Native

Favorite Games

Dota 1 and 2, Valorant, FIFA, Valheim, Lineage, Guitar Hero, Donkey Kong Country 3, Super Mario World, Goof Troop, Counter-Strike.